babajikathulluu.com 2017-06-06

# PRIVACY POLICY | Babajikathulluu.com

At Babaji ka thulluu , we give utmost importance to the privacy of our users. This privacy policy lists the kind of personal information that we receive and collect on Babaji ka thulluu and the way we use it.

**Cookies**  
Babaji ka thulluu uses cookies:

• For storage of information related to visitor preferences, for recording user-based information on the webpages a user visits or accesses  
• For customizing web page content to the visitor browser or other type of information that the visitor has agreed to send through the browser  
Log Files

Similar to other websites, Babaji ka thulluu also uses log files. The kind of information stored in these log files includes:

• IP addresses  
• Internet Service Provider  
• Kind of browser  
• Date and time stamp  
• Number of clicks for analyzing trends  
• Referring web pages or exit pages  
• Administration of site  
• Tracking user movement on the site  
• Gathering demographics

Any of this information, including IP address is not linked to any information that could personally identify the user.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie  
**  
Google makes use of cookies for serving ads on Babaji ka thulluu , but as a third party. Google uses the DART cookie for serving ads to our users based on their visit, not just to www.babajikathulluu.com but also to other websites over the Internet.

You have the option to opt out of the usage of DART cookies by going to http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html and checking and making changes based on the Google ad / content network privacy policy.

It is possible that some of our ad partners may use cookies or web beacons on our website. The names of our ad partners are:

**Google AdSense  
**  
Such third parties (ad networks / ad servers) rely on technology for sending links or ads appearing on Babaji ka thulluu directly to user’s browser. In doing so, they will automatically learn about user IP address. These third party ad networks may use different technologies like cookies, Web Beacons or JavaScript for measuring the efficacy of their ads and / or for customizing the ad content according to the user preferences.

Babaji ka thulluu doesn’t have any control and access over these cookies used by third-party ad networks / servers.

Make sure to check the privacy policies of these third party ad networks / servers to learn about them and on ways to opt out of their practices. The scope of our privacy policy cannot extend over and apply to these parties and we have no control over their activities.

You may disable cookies through your browser settings. If you want to know about the processes, kindly visit the website of your respective browser.

If any user has any queries or suggestions about our privacy policy, kindly contact us at our e-mail address: saianshee@gmail.com
